let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question:
      "Ringo, John, Paul and George are better known as which famous band?",
    answer: "The Beatles",
    options: ["The Doors", "The Who", "The Beatles", "The Beach Boys"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Gansters Paradise was a hit for which US rapper?",
    answer: "Coolio",
    options: ["Coolio", "2Pac", "Nas", "outkast"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question:
      "Dubbed the 'King of Pop' which artist released the album Thriller which went on to be the bestselling album of all time?",
    answer: "Michael Jackson",
    options: [
      "The Jackson Five",
      "Michael Jackson",
      "Prince",
      "Freddie Mercury",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Kurt Cobain was the frontman for which Grunge band?",
    answer: "Nirvana",
    options: ["Foo Fighters", "Nirvana", "Pearl Jam", "Alice In Chains"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question:
      "Which famous US singer was born in Tupelo, Mississippi in 1935 and dies in 1977 in Graceland, Tennessee?",
    answer: "Elvis Presley",
    options: ["Chuck Berry", "Little Richard", "Fats Domino", "Elvis Presley"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question:
      "Which German classical composer and pianist, was the film Immortal Beloved about>",
    answer: "Beethoven",
    options: ["Bach", "Beethoven", "Mozart", "Handel"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question:
      "What is the mane of the royal singer who turned the rain purple?",
    answer: "Prince",
    options: ["Stevie Wonder", "Elton John", "Prince", "James Brown"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question:
      "Famously part of the Rat Pack, Which singer was responsible for Come Fly with Me?",
    answer: "Frank Sinatra",
    options: ["Dean Martin", "Sammy Davis", "Joey Bishop", "Frank Sinatra"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question:
      "Who shaved their head in 2007, after checking out of a drug rehab center in LA only to check herself back in shortly thereafter?",
    answer: "Britney Spears",
    options: ["Mandy Moore", "Britney Spears", "Paris Hilton", "Lady Gaga"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which Queen of pop was married to Guy Rithcie and Sean Penn?",
    answer: "Madonna",
    options: ["Paris Hilton", "Madonna", "Donna De Lory", "Alish Chinai"],
  },
];
